<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
  <title>Sandheep Rajkumar — Writings</title>
  <link>https://sandheep.xyz</link>
  <description>Writing about things I get curious about.</description>
  <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 04:39:24 GMT</lastBuildDate>
  <item>
    <title>The Slow Death of Wonder</title>
    <link>https://sandheep.xyz/article/slowdeathofwonder</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandheep.xyz/article/slowdeathofwonder</guid>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jul 2025 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>I’ve heard people say smartphones, the internet, social media and everything else have made us less curious. And I couldn’t help but be curious about this assumption itself. And the fact that I think most people are idiots doesn’t help. I call it an assumption because the…</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>AI-Powered CAD And The Electric Lamp Problem</title>
    <link>https://sandheep.xyz/article/electriclamp</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandheep.xyz/article/electriclamp</guid>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>The reason I find myself writing this post is because I think most AI powered CAD applications suck. If you weren’t offended by the first statement and did make it to the second line, let me bring up a story known to all of us and try to map it back to my reasoning behind…</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>The Sunk Cost Fallacy</title>
    <link>https://sandheep.xyz/article/sunkcostfallacy</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandheep.xyz/article/sunkcostfallacy</guid>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>In this one, I’m going to talk about two seemingly unrelated stories from different times of my life. There are probably a thousand different lessons you could draw from how these stories came together, but I’m just focusing on one— which happens to be one of the most important…</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>How You Do Something Is How You Do Everything</title>
    <link>https://sandheep.xyz/article/howyoudosomething</link>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://sandheep.xyz/article/howyoudosomething</guid>
    <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2024 18:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
    <description>I&apos;ve always wanted to start writing but could never get myself to it because I&apos;ve never been much of a writer. So, in a truly meta fashion, I am going to use this article as an excuse to finally start and just enjoy the process. This story is from a couple months ago when I was…</description>
  </item>
</channel>
</rss>